Where... am I?
Hmm?
A pig in a straw house... It's as if...
You're mine, juicy little piggy!
That was close.
Shido?
Shido, I'm so glad to see you.
Yoshino? What's that outfit?
I don't know. I was in it when I got here.
I was told to bring this to Grandma's.
It's bizarre.
Spirit power and Angels don't work here,
so we just went with the flow.
Well, I'm one of the
Three Little Pigs, so I'm thinking...
Wait. If this is Grandma's house
in Little Red Riding Hood...
What a good little girl.
Not only did you come, but you brought
a tasty piggy with you, too!
Grandma's gone beast mode!
I'm gonna gobble both of you up!
You okay, Shido?! Yoshino?!
Tohka... Nia...
Tohka! Give 'em one of those
millet dumplings on your belt!
These?
Gee, I'm so sorry!
I get like that when I'm hangry.
Uh, right...
That's Momotaro's
millet dumplings for you!
Who knew dumplings did that?
Nia, what in the world is this?
Were we swallowed by Beelzebub?
More like we're in a world
that was created by Beelzebub.
Which story are you?
Oh, me? I'm Fatima from Silver Bullet.
That's your own fricken manga.
How do we get back to our world?
Well, Westcott's not gonna let us out.
Which means we've gotta find someone
with the power to break us out of here.
There's someone that convenient here?
I don't know, but let's find out.
The others should be
somewhere in this world, too.
Kotori! Hey, Kotori!
Concern. She won't wake up.
In that case... Oh, Shido! Over here!
Request. Kotori's in danger.
She needs a cardiac massage.
Hey! What's the big idea?!
U-Uh... Huh?
We fooled you, Kotori!
Agreement. I figured Shido's name
might wake you by the power of love.
"Ratatoskr"
What this?
I guess I'm the Little Match Girl.
This must be Westcott's doing.
This is a vision? It's so real!
Wonder! Even Shido is in it!
Kotori's feelings for Shido must've
made their way into her dreams.
I-It's supposed to be her dead grandma!
Anyway, what's your story?
What's this?
Before we knew it,
we found ourselves in a forest.
After walking a bit,
we came upon a candy house.
Explanation. Since we were hungry,
we snacked on the walls and roof.
A-ha. Hansel and Gretel, huh?
A creepy hag tried talking to us,
but we ignored her and ran away.
Agreement. She chased us
with terrifying speed.
But nobody can keep pace with us!
Truth. Kaguya had tears in her eyes
and may have peed herself.
I didn't pee myself!
We've gotta find the others
and get back to our world.
Though, where do we even start?
So many carriages today. What's happening?
I heard they're revealing something
amazing at the castle ball.
The emperor captured
a mermaid and plans to show it off!
They say it sings, "Darling! Darling!"
Scattered battles around base!
DEM Wizards and Bandersnatch confirmed!
--The Commander?!
--Can't reach her!
God help us! Misty help us!
Relax.
In times like this, losing your cool
is more dangerous than the enemy.
Don't worry. I know the crew's
capabilities better than anyone.
Well, well. You stole my thunder.
Like MARIA said, let's stay calm.
Have we heard from base?
Woodman is safe.
He's urging us to take Fraxinus
and head to Zodiac.
In that case, let's protect it
until Kotori and the others return.
Damage to our hull!
Enemies have breached the hangar!
MARIA, set Territory to 50
and activate jamming.
Acknowledged. Deploying Territory.
Our Territory neutralized the enemy.
It's deadly to machines that move
by generative magic.
Well done, Vice Commander!
But in the end, it's just Territory.
It won't stop humans and bullets.
Hands up!
Move and we'll shoot!
So this is Fraxinus...
Westcott will be pleased.
Huh?
Thank MARIA for that projection!
M-Mi...
Misty? Misty?!
How dare you hurt my Misty!
Good work, everyone.
Nakatsugawa, Shiizaki...
Y-Yes?
I've seen the usefulness
of figures and straw dolls.
I'm granting permission
to bring them on the bridge.
Misty!
Whoa. That castle
sure shouts "fairy tale."
Lots of people come through here,
so we might learn something.
C'mon, let us in!
Shido, look!
--Meanie!
--Stubborn.
Kotori? Kaguya! Yuzuru!
Shido! You're all right!
Uh, what's with the outfits?
You're one to talk.
What's the problem here?
We came to see the castle's mermaid.
I guess it cries out, "Darling! Darling!"
I see.
But this guard is a doofus!
Upset. He won't let us through!
Of course not! You're not
getting past me dressed like that!
Greetings, my friends.
Natsumi?
Sir, these are my attendants.
May they enter with me?
Uh, but...! That's...!
You don't mind, do you?
Uh... G-Go on ahead.
Um...
You little..! Get your witchcraft
outta here and don't come back!
So Natsun's Cinderella, huh?
"Natsun"?
Grr! At this rate,
we'll just have to use force!
Agreement. With our numbers,
we don't need Angels.
Hold up. Let's be smart about this.
"Ratatoskr"
Clever thinking, Kotori.
Don't let the candle go out
or we'll go back to normal.
Why am I in a dress, too?
Makes it easier
to get into the ball, right?
What a fancy castle.
That's Cinderella's ball for you.
Where's the mermaid?
I don't see it anywhere.
Ladies and gentlemen, look to the stage!
It's time to behold
the song of the mermaid!
--Miku!
Darling! Everyone! What lovely dresses!
And Darling's in Shiori mode!
Fill me in on the details!
Did anyone think to record it?!
C-Calm down. Anyway,
how did you end up here?
Before I knew it, I was in the water.
But an evil witch said she'd make me
human in exchange for my voice.
So The Little Mermaid, then.
But if you're still a mermaid...
Yup! I'd never let anyone take my voice,
so I smacked her with my tail and fled!
But then, fishermen
caught me on the beach...
What's this commotion?
The emperor!
--Wha--?!
--Oh my!
--Th-That's the rumored...
--What a wonderful outfit!
Truly! It's like a veil of mist!
Shido, everyone... I'm glad you're okay.
Y-Yeah. But... are you okay?
I don't understand.
How to put it...?
You didn't get mugged, did you?
Origami! What kind of
outfit is that?! You're naked!
Did you just...?!
Did she insult the emperor's clothes?!
I got it from wandering tailors.
Those without love for Shido can't see it.
And since you can't see it, Tohka...
Wha--?! H-Hold on!
M-My, what splendid skin-like clothes!
No need to fake it, Tohka.
It's The Emperor's New Clothes.
The Emperor's New Clothes...
I had no idea.
You didn't think it strange?
When they said you can't see it without
love, I thought I caught of glimpse of it.
I-I see...
But this is good.
We're all together again.
Yeah. And Origami is emperor.
She can use her power to search
the lands for a superhero.
"Superhero"?
Yup. There might be someone powerful
who can return us to our world.
True. With my power,
I can issue a search of the lands.
We might find an item or something.
Ooh! We'll get back
to our world in no time!
Let's start right away and--!
The wolf!
It can't be! Ogres from Onigashima!
You weren't coming,
so we came to find you!
What the hell?!
Oh, that's mine. A monster from
Silver Bullet revives in Part 2,
gets powerful in Part 3, and
comes for revenge on Fatima.
Those damn recurring villains!
So be it!
Wait! We can't use our Spirit
power here! We won't win!
Then what should we do?!
Would not the Spirits you "save"
be exposed to greater peril?
Shido, I tire hearing of this hypocrisy.
Run, you guys!
"Little Red Riding Hood"
Who the hell are you?!
Just a neighborhood high schooler.
--That's... Shido?
--What's going on?
Oh! He's from the manga we drew!
Oh, yeah! 'Cuz this world
is a mix of stories!
It's not unusual for the "Shido"
from our manga to be here.
What's more, he's like
Shido Itsuka, but not!
He's a manga hero!
He's both super cool and super strong!
You okay, me?
Y-Yeah. Thanks, me.
Now we're starting to sound like Kurumi.
This can't be good. If you're all here,
I take it Westcott's involved?
That saves the explanation.
Can we return to our world somehow?
We need to get back as soon as possible.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
This world was made by a Demon King,
which means it can be broken by an Angel.
Though I may be fiction, while in
this world, my Angel's the real deal!
Go through here to get back!
Thanks, Shido!
Hey, me.
Hmm? What's up, me?
I'm supposed to help
this Spirit named Mukuro, but...
You have doubts:
"If I hadn't sealed the Spirits' powers,
they wouldn't face so much danger.
Maybe I made the wrong choice."
I know, because you're me.
Even so, I'd go help that Spirit.
But Mukuro wants to be left alone.
True, but doesn't it seem strange to you?
She locked her heart to not be sad.
Doesn't that mean she was sad enough
at one point to resort to that?
Her words sound like an SOS to me.
For starters, what is it I want for her?
"What is it I want for her?"
I see. You're right. Thanks.
Good luck, high schooler.
You, too, neighborhood high schooler.
Took long enough, Shido.
What happened?
Did you talk with the other Shido?
Yeah, just a bit. But I'm fine now.
Let's go save Mukuro!
Commander!
We need to get to Mukuro quickly.
Prepare to launch!
Realizers in parallel drive!
Deploy Territory in avoid mode!
Fraxinus Excelsior, lift off!
"Episode 05:
'Fairy Tale'"
Fraxinus gets a new life,
but blocking their way is Ellen in Goetia.
How will this fated showdown end?
Next time: "An Opened Heart."
"Episode 06: 'An Opened Heart"'
Shido and Mukuro's destiny awaits!